{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115257205","data":{"timestamp":" 947115257205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_o-j-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115265920","data":{"timestamp":" 947115265920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-t-f"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115271657","data":{"timestamp":" 947115271657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_g-j-p"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115276169","data":{"timestamp":" 947115276169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_n-v-j"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115280077","data":{"timestamp":" 947115280077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_p-j-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115284317","data":{"timestamp":" 947115284316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_r-j-d"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115288582","data":{"timestamp":" 947115288582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_o-j-d"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115292404","data":{"timestamp":" 947115292404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_s-j-ch"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115296686","data":{"timestamp":" 947115296686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-v-s"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115300773","data":{"timestamp":" 947115300773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_v-z-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115306533","data":{"timestamp":" 947115306533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ca5c60a7-5387-4b0b-a87e-99758fcf6044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.96"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_j_v-z-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115331154","data":{"timestamp":" 947115331154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_r_g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115337787","data":{"timestamp":" 947115337787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_n_j"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115344416","data":{"timestamp":" 947115344415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_y_k"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115351047","data":{"timestamp":" 947115351047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_s_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115357681","data":{"timestamp":" 947115357681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_j_p"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115364321","data":{"timestamp":" 947115364320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_j_m"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115370986","data":{"timestamp":" 947115370986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_r_j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115377633","data":{"timestamp":" 947115377633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_j_l"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115384260","data":{"timestamp":" 947115384260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_i_h"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115390909","data":{"timestamp":" 947115390909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_w_j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115403018","data":{"timestamp":" 947115403017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a8f62ecd-3970-4bd8-ab77-782f5e5fb85d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_y_w_j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115418440","data":{"timestamp":" 947115418439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115419504","data":{"timestamp":" 947115419504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115422541","data":{"timestamp":" 947115422540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115423600","data":{"timestamp":" 947115423599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115426682","data":{"timestamp":" 947115426681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115427733","data":{"timestamp":" 947115427732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115430690","data":{"timestamp":" 947115430690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115431746","data":{"timestamp":" 947115431745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115434759","data":{"timestamp":" 947115434759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115435804","data":{"timestamp":" 947115435803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115441690","data":{"timestamp":" 947115441689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115442774","data":{"timestamp":" 947115442772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115446107","data":{"timestamp":" 947115446107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115447178","data":{"timestamp":" 947115447177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115452974","data":{"timestamp":" 947115452974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115454016","data":{"timestamp":" 947115454016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115457812","data":{"timestamp":" 947115457812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115458870","data":{"timestamp":" 947115458869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115463125","data":{"timestamp":" 947115463124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115464182","data":{"timestamp":" 947115464182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115466882","data":{"timestamp":" 947115466882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115467945","data":{"timestamp":" 947115467944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115472381","data":{"timestamp":" 947115472380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115473437","data":{"timestamp":" 947115473437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115477069","data":{"timestamp":" 947115477069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115478138","data":{"timestamp":" 947115478138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115481088","data":{"timestamp":" 947115481088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115482166","data":{"timestamp":" 947115482166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115484775","data":{"timestamp":" 947115484774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115485834","data":{"timestamp":" 947115485834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115488595","data":{"timestamp":" 947115488594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115489666","data":{"timestamp":" 947115489665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115492886","data":{"timestamp":" 947115492886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115493942","data":{"timestamp":" 947115493941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115496322","data":{"timestamp":" 947115496322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115496446","data":{"timestamp":" 947115496446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 8135821e-0c6a-4011-ac3b-f29a1d391d65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115512263","data":{"timestamp":" 947115512262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115516325","data":{"timestamp":" 947115516325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115519961","data":{"timestamp":" 947115519961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115523453","data":{"timestamp":" 947115523453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115528043","data":{"timestamp":" 947115528043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115531977","data":{"timestamp":" 947115531977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115535929","data":{"timestamp":" 947115535929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115539812","data":{"timestamp":" 947115539812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115545135","data":{"timestamp":" 947115545135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115549947","data":{"timestamp":" 947115549947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115554240","data":{"timestamp":" 947115554240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115560466","data":{"timestamp":" 947115560466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115564675","data":{"timestamp":" 947115564674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115568431","data":{"timestamp":" 947115568431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115573251","data":{"timestamp":" 947115573251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115576684","data":{"timestamp":" 947115576684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115579972","data":{"timestamp":" 947115579971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115583941","data":{"timestamp":" 947115583941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115587716","data":{"timestamp":" 947115587715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115604578","data":{"timestamp":" 947115604577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115608957","data":{"timestamp":" 947115608957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115612509","data":{"timestamp":" 947115612509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115616597","data":{"timestamp":" 947115616597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115621861","data":{"timestamp":" 947115621861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115627646","data":{"timestamp":" 947115627645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6e8e2bf1-f18c-4e21-8d19-56f472df95e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115643985","data":{"timestamp":" 947115643985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 7cb808fc-4a8d-4d84-8e8d-6d671405fead"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115689219","data":{"timestamp":" 947115689219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 7cb808fc-4a8d-4d84-8e8d-6d671405fead"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115689349","data":{"timestamp":" 947115689349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 7cb808fc-4a8d-4d84-8e8d-6d671405fead"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115742177","data":{"timestamp":" 947115742176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 7cb808fc-4a8d-4d84-8e8d-6d671405fead"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115756949","data":{"timestamp":" 947115756949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 280ee003-4e51-4b09-8bb6-d7dbe59d135b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115814418","data":{"timestamp":" 947115814416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 280ee003-4e51-4b09-8bb6-d7dbe59d135b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115814513","data":{"timestamp":" 947115814513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 280ee003-4e51-4b09-8bb6-d7dbe59d135b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115873197","data":{"timestamp":" 947115873196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 280ee003-4e51-4b09-8bb6-d7dbe59d135b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115883575","data":{"timestamp":" 947115883575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ae24973d-5372-46ac-91b7-b38c36fb9515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115937344","data":{"timestamp":" 947115937343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ae24973d-5372-46ac-91b7-b38c36fb9515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115937503","data":{"timestamp":" 947115937503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ae24973d-5372-46ac-91b7-b38c36fb9515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115963462","data":{"timestamp":" 947115963462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115967124","data":{"timestamp":" 947115967124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115970565","data":{"timestamp":" 947115970565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115974405","data":{"timestamp":" 947115974405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115977702","data":{"timestamp":" 947115977702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115980949","data":{"timestamp":" 947115980949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115984269","data":{"timestamp":" 947115984269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115987974","data":{"timestamp":" 947115987974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115991229","data":{"timestamp":" 947115991229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115997130","data":{"timestamp":" 947115997129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116001056","data":{"timestamp":" 947116001056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116004710","data":{"timestamp":" 947116004710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116008195","data":{"timestamp":" 947116008195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116011721","data":{"timestamp":" 947116011721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116015105","data":{"timestamp":" 947116015105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116018545","data":{"timestamp":" 947116018545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116022590","data":{"timestamp":" 947116022590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116026135","data":{"timestamp":" 947116026134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116029652","data":{"timestamp":" 947116029652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116033069","data":{"timestamp":" 947116033068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116036408","data":{"timestamp":" 947116036408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116054749","data":{"timestamp":" 947116054749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116061530","data":{"timestamp":" 947116061530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116065210","data":{"timestamp":" 947116065210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116069512","data":{"timestamp":" 947116069512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116075257","data":{"timestamp":" 947116075255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 19fa475a-1074-4f63-8184-2dddd85c1604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116104794","data":{"timestamp":" 947116104793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116106971","data":{"timestamp":" 947116106970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116109079","data":{"timestamp":" 947116109079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116112340","data":{"timestamp":" 947116112340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116114607","data":{"timestamp":" 947116114606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116116850","data":{"timestamp":" 947116116850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116119781","data":{"timestamp":" 947116119780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116121996","data":{"timestamp":" 947116121996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116124166","data":{"timestamp":" 947116124166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116127327","data":{"timestamp":" 947116127327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116129398","data":{"timestamp":" 947116129397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116131462","data":{"timestamp":" 947116131462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116134391","data":{"timestamp":" 947116134387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116136599","data":{"timestamp":" 947116136598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116138855","data":{"timestamp":" 947116138854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116141912","data":{"timestamp":" 947116141911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116144266","data":{"timestamp":" 947116144265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116146646","data":{"timestamp":" 947116146645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116149738","data":{"timestamp":" 947116149738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116151823","data":{"timestamp":" 947116151823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116153930","data":{"timestamp":" 947116153930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116157012","data":{"timestamp":" 947116157011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116159214","data":{"timestamp":" 947116159214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116161393","data":{"timestamp":" 947116161392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116164589","data":{"timestamp":" 947116164589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116167018","data":{"timestamp":" 947116167017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116169456","data":{"timestamp":" 947116169455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116172585","data":{"timestamp":" 947116172584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116174883","data":{"timestamp":" 947116174882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116177177","data":{"timestamp":" 947116177176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116180172","data":{"timestamp":" 947116180171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116182420","data":{"timestamp":" 947116182419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116184639","data":{"timestamp":" 947116184638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116187655","data":{"timestamp":" 947116187654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116190032","data":{"timestamp":" 947116190031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116192401","data":{"timestamp":" 947116192400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116195581","data":{"timestamp":" 947116195580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116197957","data":{"timestamp":" 947116197957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116200365","data":{"timestamp":" 947116200364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116203343","data":{"timestamp":" 947116203342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116205635","data":{"timestamp":" 947116205634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116207903","data":{"timestamp":" 947116207902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116211189","data":{"timestamp":" 947116211188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116213476","data":{"timestamp":" 947116213475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116215771","data":{"timestamp":" 947116215770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116219121","data":{"timestamp":" 947116219120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116221603","data":{"timestamp":" 947116221602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116224061","data":{"timestamp":" 947116224061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116226976","data":{"timestamp":" 947116226975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116229195","data":{"timestamp":" 947116229194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116231400","data":{"timestamp":" 947116231399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116234864","data":{"timestamp":" 947116234863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116237196","data":{"timestamp":" 947116237196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116239464","data":{"timestamp":" 947116239464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116242518","data":{"timestamp":" 947116242517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116244800","data":{"timestamp":" 947116244799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116247056","data":{"timestamp":" 947116247056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116250075","data":{"timestamp":" 947116250074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116252241","data":{"timestamp":" 947116252240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116254390","data":{"timestamp":" 947116254389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116257510","data":{"timestamp":" 947116257509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116259782","data":{"timestamp":" 947116259779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116262020","data":{"timestamp":" 947116262020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116265131","data":{"timestamp":" 947116265131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116267303","data":{"timestamp":" 947116267303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116269455","data":{"timestamp":" 947116269455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116272619","data":{"timestamp":" 947116272619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116274901","data":{"timestamp":" 947116274901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116277162","data":{"timestamp":" 947116277162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116280184","data":{"timestamp":" 947116280184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116282449","data":{"timestamp":" 947116282449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116284712","data":{"timestamp":" 947116284712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116288080","data":{"timestamp":" 947116288080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116288170","data":{"timestamp":" 947116288170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 1e97a5af-e987-48e0-8ca4-664a7f5bc05a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116303815","data":{"timestamp":" 947116303815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116304190","data":{"timestamp":" 947116304189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116304672","data":{"timestamp":" 947116304672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116305016","data":{"timestamp":" 947116305016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116305435","data":{"timestamp":" 947116305435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116305918","data":{"timestamp":" 947116305917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116306156","data":{"timestamp":" 947116306155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116309354","data":{"timestamp":" 947116309354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116309388","data":{"timestamp":" 947116309388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116310114","data":{"timestamp":" 947116310114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116310509","data":{"timestamp":" 947116310509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116310803","data":{"timestamp":" 947116310803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116311006","data":{"timestamp":" 947116311006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116311200","data":{"timestamp":" 947116311199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116311528","data":{"timestamp":" 947116311527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116311762","data":{"timestamp":" 947116311761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116314939","data":{"timestamp":" 947116314939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116315341","data":{"timestamp":" 947116315341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116317880","data":{"timestamp":" 947116317879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116318094","data":{"timestamp":" 947116318093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116318305","data":{"timestamp":" 947116318304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116321821","data":{"timestamp":" 947116321820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116325552","data":{"timestamp":" 947116325552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116326583","data":{"timestamp":" 947116326582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116329279","data":{"timestamp":" 947116329278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116329662","data":{"timestamp":" 947116329662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116330158","data":{"timestamp":" 947116330157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116330517","data":{"timestamp":" 947116330516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116330933","data":{"timestamp":" 947116330932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116331418","data":{"timestamp":" 947116331418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116331652","data":{"timestamp":" 947116331652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116334915","data":{"timestamp":" 947116334914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116334955","data":{"timestamp":" 947116334955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116335675","data":{"timestamp":" 947116335675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116336084","data":{"timestamp":" 947116336084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116336390","data":{"timestamp":" 947116336389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116336605","data":{"timestamp":" 947116336605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116336812","data":{"timestamp":" 947116336811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116337145","data":{"timestamp":" 947116337145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116337385","data":{"timestamp":" 947116337384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116340026","data":{"timestamp":" 947116340024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116340133","data":{"timestamp":" 947116340133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" bbe54ee0-b89d-40eb-adae-4f019e742e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116381957","data":{"timestamp":" 947116381957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116393193","data":{"timestamp":" 947116393192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116394849","data":{"timestamp":" 947116394848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116397297","data":{"timestamp":" 947116397296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116398906","data":{"timestamp":" 947116398905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116401109","data":{"timestamp":" 947116401108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116402709","data":{"timestamp":" 947116402708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116405951","data":{"timestamp":" 947116405951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116407560","data":{"timestamp":" 947116407559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116411017","data":{"timestamp":" 947116411017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116412608","data":{"timestamp":" 947116412607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116415356","data":{"timestamp":" 947116415355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116416971","data":{"timestamp":" 947116416970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116420195","data":{"timestamp":" 947116420194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116421837","data":{"timestamp":" 947116421836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116424189","data":{"timestamp":" 947116424189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116425831","data":{"timestamp":" 947116425830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kofia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116430493","data":{"timestamp":" 947116430492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kofia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116432123","data":{"timestamp":" 947116432122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116434529","data":{"timestamp":" 947116434528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" START_KITENGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116436833","data":{"timestamp":" 947116436833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116438450","data":{"timestamp":" 947116438450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116441162","data":{"timestamp":" 947116441162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116442791","data":{"timestamp":" 947116442790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116445562","data":{"timestamp":" 947116445562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116447199","data":{"timestamp":" 947116447198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116455389","data":{"timestamp":" 947116455388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116457010","data":{"timestamp":" 947116457010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116459670","data":{"timestamp":" 947116459670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116461299","data":{"timestamp":" 947116461299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116465840","data":{"timestamp":" 947116465839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116467453","data":{"timestamp":" 947116467452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116473533","data":{"timestamp":" 947116473533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116475149","data":{"timestamp":" 947116475148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" KITAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116478989","data":{"timestamp":" 947116478989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" KITAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116480616","data":{"timestamp":" 947116480615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116485127","data":{"timestamp":" 947116485126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116486764","data":{"timestamp":" 947116486764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116492280","data":{"timestamp":" 947116492279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116493896","data":{"timestamp":" 947116493895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116496885","data":{"timestamp":" 947116496884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" START_KIKOMBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116499210","data":{"timestamp":" 947116499209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116500817","data":{"timestamp":" 947116500817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116506646","data":{"timestamp":" 947116506645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116508262","data":{"timestamp":" 947116508261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kalamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116510974","data":{"timestamp":" 947116510973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kalamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116512597","data":{"timestamp":" 947116512596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116514794","data":{"timestamp":" 947116514793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116516445","data":{"timestamp":" 947116516444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" KINU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116518847","data":{"timestamp":" 947116518846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" KINU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116520463","data":{"timestamp":" 947116520462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" katikati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116526817","data":{"timestamp":" 947116526817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" katikati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116528434","data":{"timestamp":" 947116528433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116531465","data":{"timestamp":" 947116531465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116533097","data":{"timestamp":" 947116533096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116536210","data":{"timestamp":" 947116536209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116537813","data":{"timestamp":" 947116537812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116540454","data":{"timestamp":" 947116540453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116542082","data":{"timestamp":" 947116542081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116544743","data":{"timestamp":" 947116544742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116546374","data":{"timestamp":" 947116546373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kundi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116550680","data":{"timestamp":" 947116550679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kundi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116552245","data":{"timestamp":" 947116552244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116555064","data":{"timestamp":" 947116555064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116557077","data":{"timestamp":" 947116557076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116557210","data":{"timestamp":" 947116557210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" ed49afa0-cd4c-4077-8a3f-b3a9aca033da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116571554","data":{"timestamp":" 947116571554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116575082","data":{"timestamp":" 947116575081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116576681","data":{"timestamp":" 947116576681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116584668","data":{"timestamp":" 947116584667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" START_KIBOKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116587141","data":{"timestamp":" 947116587141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116588755","data":{"timestamp":" 947116588755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116595769","data":{"timestamp":" 947116595769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116597408","data":{"timestamp":" 947116597407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116600174","data":{"timestamp":" 947116600173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116601789","data":{"timestamp":" 947116601788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116605048","data":{"timestamp":" 947116605047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116606671","data":{"timestamp":" 947116606670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116609114","data":{"timestamp":" 947116609113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116610754","data":{"timestamp":" 947116610754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116613509","data":{"timestamp":" 947116613508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116615143","data":{"timestamp":" 947116615142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116617454","data":{"timestamp":" 947116617453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116619052","data":{"timestamp":" 947116619052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kofia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116621484","data":{"timestamp":" 947116621484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kofia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116623113","data":{"timestamp":" 947116623112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116625868","data":{"timestamp":" 947116625868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116627497","data":{"timestamp":" 947116627496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116630133","data":{"timestamp":" 947116630132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116631758","data":{"timestamp":" 947116631757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116634336","data":{"timestamp":" 947116634335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116635944","data":{"timestamp":" 947116635944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116638214","data":{"timestamp":" 947116638214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116639842","data":{"timestamp":" 947116639841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116646287","data":{"timestamp":" 947116646286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116647912","data":{"timestamp":" 947116647911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116650512","data":{"timestamp":" 947116650512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116652131","data":{"timestamp":" 947116652130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116654787","data":{"timestamp":" 947116654787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116656419","data":{"timestamp":" 947116656418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" KITAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116659707","data":{"timestamp":" 947116659706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" KITAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116661296","data":{"timestamp":" 947116661295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116664173","data":{"timestamp":" 947116664173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116665792","data":{"timestamp":" 947116665791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116669087","data":{"timestamp":" 947116669087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116670713","data":{"timestamp":" 947116670713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116673690","data":{"timestamp":" 947116673689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116675310","data":{"timestamp":" 947116675310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116681112","data":{"timestamp":" 947116681111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" START_KIJIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116687264","data":{"timestamp":" 947116687264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116688890","data":{"timestamp":" 947116688889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kalamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116691742","data":{"timestamp":" 947116691741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kalamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116693345","data":{"timestamp":" 947116693344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116695647","data":{"timestamp":" 947116695646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116697258","data":{"timestamp":" 947116697257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" KINU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116699547","data":{"timestamp":" 947116699546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" KINU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116701145","data":{"timestamp":" 947116701144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" katikati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116704128","data":{"timestamp":" 947116704128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" katikati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116705713","data":{"timestamp":" 947116705712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116720427","data":{"timestamp":" 947116720427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116722045","data":{"timestamp":" 947116722045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116726883","data":{"timestamp":" 947116726882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116728492","data":{"timestamp":" 947116728491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116734032","data":{"timestamp":" 947116734031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116735619","data":{"timestamp":" 947116735618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116738765","data":{"timestamp":" 947116738764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116740360","data":{"timestamp":" 947116740359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kundi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116743380","data":{"timestamp":" 947116743380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kundi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116744993","data":{"timestamp":" 947116744993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116749456","data":{"timestamp":" 947116749456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" START_KIPEPEO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116751337","data":{"timestamp":" 947116751336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116753347","data":{"timestamp":" 947116753346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116753415","data":{"timestamp":" 947116753415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" a5905d0f-d1c9-4b4f-8724-19a601c9677b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116767442","data":{"timestamp":" 947116767441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116773094","data":{"timestamp":" 947116773094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116774729","data":{"timestamp":" 947116774728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116783125","data":{"timestamp":" 947116783124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116784765","data":{"timestamp":" 947116784764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116788296","data":{"timestamp":" 947116788295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116789878","data":{"timestamp":" 947116789877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116792465","data":{"timestamp":" 947116792464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116794075","data":{"timestamp":" 947116794074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116801702","data":{"timestamp":" 947116801702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" START_KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116803160","data":{"timestamp":" 947116803160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116804783","data":{"timestamp":" 947116804782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116807529","data":{"timestamp":" 947116807529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116809155","data":{"timestamp":" 947116809154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116811490","data":{"timestamp":" 947116811490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116813099","data":{"timestamp":" 947116813099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116815607","data":{"timestamp":" 947116815606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116817242","data":{"timestamp":" 947116817241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kofia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116819691","data":{"timestamp":" 947116819691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kofia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116821296","data":{"timestamp":" 947116821295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116830684","data":{"timestamp":" 947116830684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116832314","data":{"timestamp":" 947116832313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116836614","data":{"timestamp":" 947116836612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116838226","data":{"timestamp":" 947116838226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116841563","data":{"timestamp":" 947116841562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116843178","data":{"timestamp":" 947116843178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116846088","data":{"timestamp":" 947116846087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116847690","data":{"timestamp":" 947116847690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116851991","data":{"timestamp":" 947116851991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116853580","data":{"timestamp":" 947116853580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116857625","data":{"timestamp":" 947116857625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" START_KICHWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116860156","data":{"timestamp":" 947116860155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" START_KICHWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116861738","data":{"timestamp":" 947116861737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116863358","data":{"timestamp":" 947116863357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116873270","data":{"timestamp":" 947116873270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116874860","data":{"timestamp":" 947116874859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" KITAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116881557","data":{"timestamp":" 947116881556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" START_KITAMBAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116885405","data":{"timestamp":" 947116885405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" KITAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116887018","data":{"timestamp":" 947116887017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116890948","data":{"timestamp":" 947116890948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116892573","data":{"timestamp":" 947116892573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116896988","data":{"timestamp":" 947116896988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116898599","data":{"timestamp":" 947116898598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116902976","data":{"timestamp":" 947116902975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116904584","data":{"timestamp":" 947116904582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116907333","data":{"timestamp":" 947116907332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" START_KIJIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116910288","data":{"timestamp":" 947116910288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116911915","data":{"timestamp":" 947116911914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kalamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116916146","data":{"timestamp":" 947116916146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kalamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116917745","data":{"timestamp":" 947116917744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116921101","data":{"timestamp":" 947116921100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116922705","data":{"timestamp":" 947116922704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" KINU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116925679","data":{"timestamp":" 947116925679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" KINU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116927298","data":{"timestamp":" 947116927297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" katikati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116931275","data":{"timestamp":" 947116931275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" katikati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116932893","data":{"timestamp":" 947116932893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116936415","data":{"timestamp":" 947116936415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116938019","data":{"timestamp":" 947116938019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116940527","data":{"timestamp":" 947116940526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" START_KWAHERI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116945015","data":{"timestamp":" 947116945015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116946577","data":{"timestamp":" 947116946576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116949881","data":{"timestamp":" 947116949881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116951500","data":{"timestamp":" 947116951500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116956278","data":{"timestamp":" 947116956277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116957441","data":{"timestamp":" 947116957441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kundi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116957876","data":{"timestamp":" 947116957875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kundi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116969754","data":{"timestamp":" 947116969753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kundi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116969854","data":{"timestamp":" 947116969854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 81e04a6a-bf73-4570-96fe-44a8600244a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kundi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947116995733","data":{"timestamp":" 947116995733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_o-j-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117000320","data":{"timestamp":" 947117000319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-g-n"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117007614","data":{"timestamp":" 947117007614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-g-n"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117011928","data":{"timestamp":" 947117011927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_f-k-b"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117026181","data":{"timestamp":" 947117026181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_l-w-k"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117029975","data":{"timestamp":" 947117029975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_m-k-s"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117034468","data":{"timestamp":" 947117034468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_s-k-n"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117038330","data":{"timestamp":" 947117038330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_u-d-k"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117042109","data":{"timestamp":" 947117042109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_o-k-d"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117045680","data":{"timestamp":" 947117045680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-g-a"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117056277","data":{"timestamp":" 947117056277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-o-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117062064","data":{"timestamp":" 947117062062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" b2c6e131-bfe4-4bb7-9a5b-70ca772d28a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-o-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117080572","data":{"timestamp":" 947117080572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_w-v-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117086258","data":{"timestamp":" 947117086257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_w-v-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117098330","data":{"timestamp":" 947117098330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_w-v-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117110088","data":{"timestamp":" 947117110088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_t-k-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117116953","data":{"timestamp":" 947117116952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_b-k-l"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117128924","data":{"timestamp":" 947117128924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_ch-k-b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117137767","data":{"timestamp":" 947117137767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_h-k-l"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117142194","data":{"timestamp":" 947117142193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_n-u-k"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117144925","data":{"timestamp":" 947117144925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_l-v-k"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117150848","data":{"timestamp":" 947117150848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_l-v-k"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117154576","data":{"timestamp":" 947117154575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-h-y"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117159359","data":{"timestamp":" 947117159358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_l-z-k"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117163385","data":{"timestamp":" 947117163385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_i-h-k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117169169","data":{"timestamp":" 947117169168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 6fbfe568-48bd-4538-9ba3-fe01cde4eb66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_k_i-h-k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117185649","data":{"timestamp":" 947117185649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_ch-k-b"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117193942","data":{"timestamp":" 947117193942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_t-k-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117197873","data":{"timestamp":" 947117197873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_b-k-l"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117202086","data":{"timestamp":" 947117202086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_l-v-k"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117205810","data":{"timestamp":" 947117205810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_i-h-k"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117210517","data":{"timestamp":" 947117210517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_n-u-k"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117215180","data":{"timestamp":" 947117215180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_l-z-k"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117219461","data":{"timestamp":" 947117219460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_h-k-l"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117223135","data":{"timestamp":" 947117223135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_w-v-k"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117227177","data":{"timestamp":" 947117227177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-h-y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117232975","data":{"timestamp":" 947117232972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-h-y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117256257","data":{"timestamp":" 947117256257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" da7c4779-1627-4906-bd9d-093bf7947faf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-h-y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117276827","data":{"timestamp":" 947117276827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 26b16793-10ca-4ebb-9c4a-9aad49d810c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117277544","data":{"timestamp":" 947117277543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 26b16793-10ca-4ebb-9c4a-9aad49d810c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117277604","data":{"timestamp":" 947117277603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 26b16793-10ca-4ebb-9c4a-9aad49d810c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117308101","data":{"timestamp":" 947117308101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 26b16793-10ca-4ebb-9c4a-9aad49d810c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117364992","data":{"timestamp":" 947117364991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117378807","data":{"timestamp":" 947117378806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117382763","data":{"timestamp":" 947117382762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117387147","data":{"timestamp":" 947117387147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117391445","data":{"timestamp":" 947117391445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117396467","data":{"timestamp":" 947117396467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117402513","data":{"timestamp":" 947117402513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117409899","data":{"timestamp":" 947117409898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117421582","data":{"timestamp":" 947117421582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117430825","data":{"timestamp":" 947117430825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117434689","data":{"timestamp":" 947117434688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117444965","data":{"timestamp":" 947117444965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117448845","data":{"timestamp":" 947117448845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117452513","data":{"timestamp":" 947117452513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117456650","data":{"timestamp":" 947117456649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117460742","data":{"timestamp":" 947117460742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117464981","data":{"timestamp":" 947117464981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117470072","data":{"timestamp":" 947117470072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117487718","data":{"timestamp":" 947117487718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117498209","data":{"timestamp":" 947117498209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117502985","data":{"timestamp":" 947117502985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117506439","data":{"timestamp":" 947117506439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117510303","data":{"timestamp":" 947117510303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117515693","data":{"timestamp":" 947117515693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117521484","data":{"timestamp":" 947117521484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117577611","data":{"timestamp":" 947117577610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_023403"," gameId":" 75c194d8-9d07-4b45-8061-b9504f62eb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}